https://www.gcer.org/about-us/privacy-policy/

Who we are
Our website address is: https://www.gcer.org.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture (if applicable) is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website or we upload them for you (if applicable), you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Please use the contact form on the right side of this page to contact us with any questions or you may contact an individual by navigating to our “Contact Us” page.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
Your information may be shared with aerc.org if you are a participant in our annual endurance ride. If you are a member of GCER, your name and email address may be shared with other members. Otherwise GCER does not share or sell your information to third parties.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
For any questions you may contact the web administrator via the contact form to the right or you may mail an inquiry to our PO Box as listed in the footer.
Additional information
How we protect your data
Your data is stored securely in password-protected online storage accessible only by the web administrator, treasurer and ride secretary or as outlined in “Who we share your data with”. Any data other than your name and email address is stored outside of the server for gcer.org in a separate password-protected environment. All personal data received via paper format is converted to electronic format and subsequently stored in password-protected online storage. The paper is subsequently destroyed by secure destruct shredding or burning.
What third parties we receive data from
We may receive or compare information obtained from aerc.org in order to validate your information for participation in our annual ride.
